(Leonard:)All right.
(Howard:)Sheldon, when this whole thing
with the parking space started...
(Howard:)...I had no idea
just how much of a crazy bastard...
(Raj:)Howard, that's not how we practiced it.
(Howard:)I had no idea
how much that spot meant to you.
Anyway, I called President Seibert...
(Howard:)...and told him
it's not worth fighting over the spot...
(Howard:)...so you keep it...
(Howard:)...and I'll park in the structure
across the street.
(Sheldon:)Well, Howard, thank you.
That's quite a gesture on your part.
(Sheldon:)You've shown yourself
to be the bigger man.
(Sheldon:)- Thank you.
- Which I find totally unacceptable.
(Sheldon:)I must be the bigger man.
(Sheldon:)Therefore, you may use my spot...
(Sheldon:)...until such time as I learn to drive
or get a Batmobile.